University of Connecticut 1998.0185
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1935-1962
  - 1959-1960
    - Su (Box 24:, Folder 43)
    - Summer theatre (Box 24:, Folder 44)
    - T (Box 24:, Folder 45)
    - Tappan, Frances M. - Tech. Dir. School of Physical Therapy (Box 24:, Folder 46)
    - Teaching loads (Box 24:, Folder 47)
    - To (Box 24:, Folder 48)
    - Torgerson, Harold - Dean, School of Engineering (Box 24:, Folder 49)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 24:, Folder 50)
    - Trail, J. M. (Box 24:, Folder 51)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. - Dean, School of Social Work (Box 24:, Folder 52)
    - T.V. (Box 24:, Folder 53)
    - U (Box 24:, Folder 54)
    - University Club (Box 24:, Folder 55)
    - University high school budget, 1960 - 1961 (Box 24:, Folder 56)
    - University secondary school (Box 24:, Folder 57)
    - University Security Police, 1959-1960 (Box 24:, Folder 58)
    - University Senate (Box 24:, Folder 59)
    - U.S.D.A. (Box 24:, Folder 60)
    - U.S. Department Health, Education and Welfare (Box 24:, Folder 61)
    - V (Box 24:, Folder 62)
    - Van Bibber, George - Director, School of Physical Education (Box 24:, Folder 63)
    - Veterinary Science building (Box 24:, Folder 64)
    - Von der Mehden, J. Louis Rehearsal and Recital Hall (Box 24:, Folder 65)
    - W (Box 24:, Folder 66)
    - Waring, Charles E. (Box 24:, Folder 67)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 24:, Folder 68)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 24:, Folder 69)
    - Waugh, Albert E. - Provost (Box 24:, Folder 70)
    - We (Box 24:, Folder 71)
    - Wh (Box 24:, Folder 72)
    - W.H.U.S. (Box 24:, Folder 73)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. - Dean, Graduate School (Box 24:, Folder 74)
    - Wi (Box 24:, Folder 75)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. - Dean, School of Nursing (Box 24:, Folder 76)
    - Wo (Box 24:, Folder 77)
    - X - Y (Box 24:, Folder 78)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 24:, Folder 79)
    - Young, W. B. - Dean, College of Agriculture (Box 24:, Folder 80)
  - 1960-1961
    - A (Box 25:, Folder 81)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. - Dean, School of Business Admin. (Box 25:, Folder 82)
    - Administrative council (Box 25:, Folder 83)
    - Administrative reports (Box 25:, Folder 84)
    - Advisers (Box 26:, Folder 1)
    - Air Force (Box 26:, Folder 2)
    - Alumni (Box 26:, Folder 3)
    - American Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities (Box 26:, Folder 4)
    - American Council - Higher Education and National Affairs (Box 26:, Folder 5)
    - American Council - report on questionnaires (Box 26:, Folder 6)
    - American Council on Education (Box 26:, Folder 7)
    - An (Box 26:, Folder 8)
    - Architects (Box 26:, Folder 9)
    - Archons (Box 26:, Folder 10)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 26:, Folder 11)
    - Attorney General (Box 26:, Folder 12)
    - Auditor's reports, 1960-1961 (Box 26:, Folder 13)
    - B (Box 26:, Folder 14)
    - Bailey, Clark L. (Box 26:, Folder 15)
    - Bailey, Barbara (Mrs. John M.) (Trustee) (Box 26:, Folder 16)
    - Bain, David - Activities coordinator (Box 26:, Folder 17)
    - Be (Box 26:, Folder 18)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 26:, Folder 19)
    - Bequests (Box 26:, Folder 20)
    - Bi (Box 26:, Folder 21)
    - Bishop, Merlin (Trustee) (Box 26:, Folder 22)
    - Bo (Box 26:, Folder 23)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 26:, Folder 24)
    - Booklets and material mailed out (Box 26:, Folder 25)
    - Borge, Victor (Box 26:, Folder 26)
    - Br (Box 26:, Folder 27)
    - Brammell, P. Roy (Box 26:, Folder 28)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 26:, Folder 29)
    - Budget (Box 26:, Folder 30)
    - Budget division, State (Box 26:, Folder 31)
    - Busses (Box 26:, Folder 32)
    - C (Box 26:, Folder 33)
    - Campus (Box 26:, Folder 34)
    - CANEL (Box 26:, Folder 35)
    - Capital projects (Box 26:, Folder 36)
    - Carter, W. Harrison (Box 26:, Folder 37)
    - Ce (Box 26:, Folder 38)
    - Christian, J. O. - Director, Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 26:, Folder 39)
    - Civil defense (Box 26:, Folder 40)
    - Co (Box 26:, Folder 41)
    - Cohen, Summer - Men's Housing (Box 26:, Folder 42)
    - College entrance examinations (Box 26:, Folder 43)
    - Commencement (Box 26:, Folder 44)
    - Committee - Ad hoc, faculty - administration (Box 26:, Folder 45)
    - Committee letters (Box 26:, Folder 46)
    - Committee minutes (Box 26:, Folder 47)
    - Committee reports (Box 26:, Folder 48)
    - Computer Center (Box 26:, Folder 49)
    - Conferences (Box 26:, Folder 50)
    - Connecticut Citizens for the Public Schools (Box 26:, Folder 51)
    - Connecitcut Council for Pre - college Science Education, Inc. (Box 26:, Folder 52)
    - Connecticut Educational Television Corporation (Box 26:, Folder 53)
    - Connecticut State Grange (Box 26:, Folder 54)
    - Contracts (Box 26:, Folder 55)
    - Coo, 1960-1961 (Box 27:, Folder 1)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education (Box 27:, Folder 2)
    - Cr (Box 27:, Folder 3)
    - D (Box 27:, Folder 4)
    - Deans and directors (Box 27:, Folder 5)
    - Dining hall (Box 27:, Folder 6)
    - Donahue, A. J. Jr. (Trustee) (Box 27:, Folder 7)
    - Dormitories (Box 27:, Folder 8)
    - E (Box 27:, Folder 9)
    - Education, School of - building (Box 27:, Folder 10)
    - Education, State Department of (Box 27:, Folder 11)
    - En (Box 27:, Folder 12)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 27:, Folder 13)
    - Enrollments (Box 27:, Folder 14)
    - Evans, John M. - Fiscal vice president (Box 27:, Folder 15)
    - Extension (Box 27:, Folder 16)
    - F (Box 27:, Folder 17)
    - Fees (Box 27:, Folder 18)
    - Fi (Box 27:, Folder 19)
    - Finance Committee - Elmer S. Watson, chairman (Box 27:, Folder 20)
    - Finance and Control Dept. of - George J. Conkling, commissioner (Box 27:, Folder 21)
    - Financial statements (Box 27:, Folder 22)
    - Fine Arts (Box 27:, Folder 23)
    - Fingles, Franklin O. (Box 27:, Folder 24)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 27:, Folder 25)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 27:, Folder 26)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 27:, Folder 27)
    - Ge (Box 27:, Folder 28)
    - Gi (Box 27:, Folder 29)
    - Gill, Joseph N. (Trustee) (Box 27:, Folder 30)
    - Governor of Connecticut - Abraham A. Ribicoff (Box 27:, Folder 31)
    - H (Box 27:, Folder 32)
    - Har (Box 27:, Folder 33)
    - Hartford Branch - W. R. Griswold, supervisor (Box 27:, Folder 34)
    - Health service - Dr. LeRoy, director (Box 27:, Folder 35)
    - Hewitt, Harold O. - Dean, School of Pharmacy (Box 27:, Folder 36)
    - Hockey rink (Box 27:, Folder 37)
    - Holt, Guy B. (Trustee) (Box 27:, Folder 38)
    - Honors day (Box 27:, Folder 39)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. - Dean, School of Law (Box 27:, Folder 40)
    - Hu (Box 27:, Folder 41)
    - I (Box 27:, Folder 42)
    - Inaugurations (Box 27:, Folder 43)
    - Institute of Cellular Biology - Hugh Clark, 1960-1961 (Box 27:, Folder 44)
    - Institute of counseling and Guidance Training - E. A. Wicas (Box 27:, Folder 45)
    - Institute of Food Science and Nutrition (Box 27:, Folder 46)
    - Institute of Gerontology - Don - P. Kent (Box 27:, Folder 47)
    - Institute of Marine Research - John S. Rankin (Box 27:, Folder 48)
    - Institute of Public Service - Beldon Schaffer (Box 27:, Folder 49)
    - Institute for Secondary School Teachers of Physics (Box 27:, Folder 50)
    - Institute for Teachers of Science (Box 27:, Folder 51)
    - J (Box 27:, Folder 52)
    - Joint Advisory Panel on ROTC (Box 27:, Folder 53)
    - Joint Council on Educational Television (Box 28:, Folder 1)
    - Joint Projects office - Allan Ostar (Box 28:, Folder 2)
    - Jorgenson, A. N. (Box 28:, Folder 3)
    - K (Box 28:, Folder 4)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 28:, Folder 5)
    - L (Box 28:, Folder 6)
    - Labor Management Institute (Box 28:, Folder 7)
    - Land Grant College Association (Box 28:, Folder 8)
    - Land Grant Committee on Traffic Safety (Box 28:, Folder 9)
    - Learning Resource Institute (Box 28:, Folder 10)
    - Legislation, Federal (Box 28:, Folder 11)
    - Legislature, State (Box 28:, Folder 12)
    - Li (Box 28:, Folder 13)
    - Liaison Committee - Bd. Of Trustees, State Bd. Of Education. (Box 28:, Folder 14)
    - Liaison Committee - U. Conn, U. of Hartford (Box 28:, Folder 15)
    - Library - James E. Skipper (Box 28:, Folder 16)
    - Life Science building (Box 28:, Folder 17)
    - Lo (Box 28:, Folder 18)
    - M (Box 28:, Folder 19)
    - Manning, Stuart H. - Acting Director, University Extension (Box 28:, Folder 20)
    - Mansfield, J. Kenneth (Trustee) (Box 28:, Folder 21)
    - Maps of health care resources (Box 28:, Folder 22)
    - May, Elizabeth E. - Dean, School of Home Economics (Box 28:, Folder 23)
    - McMahon, Brien - Lecture Series (Box 29:, Folder 1)
    - Mi (Box 29:, Folder 2)
    - Military ball (Box 29:, Folder 3)
    - Military day (Box 29:, Folder 4)
    - Military Department (Box 29:, Folder 5)
    - Mo (Box 29:, Folder 6)
    - N (Box 29:, Folder 7)
    - National Advisory Panel on ROTC Affairs (Box 29:, Folder 8)
    - National Association of State Universities (Box 29:, Folder 9)
    - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 29:, Folder 10)
    - National Education Association, 1960-1961 (Box 29:, Folder 11)
    - National Institute for Atmospheric Research (Box 29:, Folder 12)
    - National Library Week (Box 29:, Folder 13)
    - National Safety Council (Box 29:, Folder 14)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 29:, Folder 15)
    - Nelson, Don (Box 29:, Folder 16)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 29:, Folder 17)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (Box 29:, Folder 18)
    - New England Council (Box 29:, Folder 19)
    - New England Land Grant State Universities (Box 29:, Folder 20)
    - Norris, Robert - Dean, Adult Education Services (Box 29:, Folder 21)
    - Northby, Arwood S. (Box 29:, Folder 22)
    - North dormitories (Box 29:, Folder 23)
    - Nuclear reactors (Box 29:, Folder 24)
    - O (Box 29:, Folder 25)
    - P (Box 29:, Folder 26)
    - Peterson, M. Elizabeth (Trustee) (Box 29:, Folder 27)
    - Pharmacy Research addition (Box 29:, Folder 28)
    - Powers, John E. - Director, Placement (Box 29:, Folder 29)
    - Public Works Department (Box 29:, Folder 30)
    - R (Box 29:, Folder 31)
    - Re (Box 29:, Folder 32)
    - Real estate (Box 29:, Folder 33)
    - Religious education (Box 29:, Folder 34)
    - Research corporation (Box 29:, Folder 35)
    - Research foundation (Box 29:, Folder 36)
    - Research Grants (Box 30:, Folder 1)
    - Ro (Box 30:, Folder 2)
    - Roberts, Thomas E. - Admissions officer (Box 30:, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 30:, Folder 4)
    - Room Assignments (Box 30:, Folder 5)
    - Ryan, J. Ray (Trustee) (Box 30:, Folder 6)
    - S (Box 30:, Folder 7)
    - Sanders, William J. (Trustee) (Box 30:, Folder 8)
    - Schneller, Richard (Trustee) (Box 30:, Folder 9)
    - Scholarships, financial aids and gifts (Box 30:, Folder 10)
    - Science talent awards (Box 30:, Folder 11)
    - Sistare, Willard M. - Manager, Auditorium (Box 30:, Folder 12)
    - South dormitory (Box 30:, Folder 13)
    - Speaking engagements (Box 30:, Folder 14)
    - Speeches (Box 30:, Folder 15)
    - St (Box 30:, Folder 16)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 30:, Folder 17)
    - State Building Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 30:, Folder 18)
    - State Comptroller (Box 30:, Folder 19)
    - State Highway Department (Box 30:, Folder 20)
    - State personnel (Box 30:, Folder 21)
    - State Public Utilities (Box 30:, Folder 22)
    - Student Senate (Box 30:, Folder 23)
    - Students, letters re (Box 30:, Folder 24)
    - Student Union board and building (Box 30:, Folder 25)
    - Summer theatre (Box 30:, Folder 26)
    - T (Box 30:, Folder 27)
    - Tappan, Frances M. - Tech. Dir., School of Physical Therapy (Box 30:, Folder 28)
    - Teaching loads (Box 30:, Folder 29)
    - To (Box 30:, Folder 30)
    - Torgersen, Harold - Dean, School of Engineering (Box 30:, Folder 31)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 30:, Folder 32)
    - Trail, John M. (Box 30:, Folder 33)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. - Dean, School of Social Work (Box 30:, Folder 34)
    - U (Box 30:, Folder 35)
    - University band (Box 30:, Folder 36)
    - University club (Box 30:, Folder 37)
    - University museum (Box 30:, Folder 38)
    - University scholars (Box 30:, Folder 39)
    - University secondary School (Box 30:, Folder 40)
    - University Senate (Box 30:, Folder 41)
    - U.S.D.A. (Box 30:, Folder 42)
    - U.S. Department Heath, Education and Welfare (Box 30:, Folder 43)
    - V (Box 31:, Folder 1)
    - Van Bibber, E. George - Dir., Physical Education (Box 31:, Folder 2)
    - Veterinary School building (Box 31:, Folder 3)
    - Von der Mehden, J. Louis - Rehearsal and Recital Hall (Box 31:, Folder 4)
    - W (Box 31:, Folder 5)
    - Waring, Charles (Box 31:, Folder 6)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 31:, Folder 7)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 31:, Folder 8)
    - Waugh, A. E. - Provost (Box 31:, Folder 9)
    - We (Box 31:, Folder 10)
    - Wh (Box 31:, Folder 11)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. - Dean, Graduate School (Box 31:, Folder 12)
    - W.H.U.S. (Box 31:, Folder 13)
    - Wi (Box 31:, Folder 14)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. - Dean, School of Nursing (Box 31:, Folder 15)
    - Wo (Box 31:, Folder 16)
    - X - Y, 1960-1961 (Box 31:, Folder 17)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 31:, Folder 18)
    - Young, W. B. - Dean, College of Agriculture (Box 31:, Folder 19)
    - Z (Box 31:, Folder 20)
  - 1961-1962
    - A (Box 31:, Folder 21)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. - Dean, School of Bus. Admin. (Box 31:, Folder 22)
    - Administrative report (Box 31:, Folder 23)
    - Advisers (Box 31:, Folder 24)
    - African Scholarship program (Box 31:, Folder 25)
    - Air Force (Box 31:, Folder 26)
    - Alumni (Box 31:, Folder 27)
    - American Council on Education (Box 31:, Folder 28)
    - Atomic Engorge Commission (Box 31:, Folder 29)
    - Austin, Joseph H. - Comptroller (Box 31:, Folder 30)
    - B (Box 31:, Folder 31)
    - Babbige, Homer D., Jr. (Box 31:, Folder 32)
    - Bailey, Barbara (Mrs. John) (Trustee) (Box 31:, Folder 33)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 31:, Folder 34)
    - Bequests (Box 31:, Folder 35)
    - Biographical data - A. N. Jorgensen (Box 31:, Folder 36)
    - Bishop, Merlin D. (Trustee) (Box 31:, Folder 37)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 31:, Folder 38)
    - Booklets mailed out (Box 31:, Folder 39)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 31:, Folder 40)
    - Budget (Box 31:, Folder 41)
    - Budget division, State (Box 31:, Folder 42)
    - C (Box 31:, Folder 43)
    - Campus (Box 31:, Folder 44)
    - Capital projects (Box 31:, Folder 45)
    - Carter, W. Harrison - Dean, Arts and Sciences (Box 31:, Folder 46)
    - Carter, W. Harrison - National Defense (Box 31:, Folder 47)
    - Christian, J. O. (Box 31:, Folder 48)
    - Clippings and releases (Box 31:, Folder 49)
    - Co (Box 31:, Folder 50)
    - Cold Spring Harbor Lab. (Box 31:, Folder 51)
    - College entrance examination board (Box 31:, Folder 52)
    - Commencement (Box 31:, Folder 53)
    - Committee - Ad hoc, trustees - Admin. - faculty (Box 31:, Folder 54)
    - Committee letters (Box 31:, Folder 55)
    - Committee minutes (Box 31:, Folder 56)
    - Committee reports, 1961-1962 (Box 31:, Folder 57)
    - Computer Center (Box 31:, Folder 58)
    - Conferences (Box 31:, Folder 59)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 31:, Folder 60)
    - Connecticut Education Association (Box 31:, Folder 61)
    - Connecticut Educational Television Corp. (Box 31:, Folder 62)
    - Contracts (Box 31:, Folder 63)
    - D (Box 32:, Folder 1)
    - Dean's council (Box 32:, Folder 2)
    - Deans and directors (Box 32:, Folder 3)
    - Donahue, A. J. (Trustee) (Box 32:, Folder 4)
    - Driscoll, Paul J. (Trustee) (Box 32:, Folder 5)
    - E (Box 32:, Folder 6)
    - Education, School of (Box 32:, Folder 7)
    - Education, State Department of (Box 32:, Folder 8)
    - Engineering Research Center (Box 32:, Folder 9)
    - Enrollments (Box 32:, Folder 10)
    - Evans, John M. - Fiscal Vice - President (Box 32:, Folder 11)
    - F (Box 32:, Folder 12)
    - Fees (Box 32:, Folder 13)
    - Finance and Control, Department of (Box 32:, Folder 14)
    - Financial Aids (Box 32:, Folder 15)
    - Fine Arts (Box 32:, Folder 16)
    - Fingles, Franklin O. - Registrar (Box 32:, Folder 17)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 32:, Folder 18)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 32:, Folder 19)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 32:, Folder 20)
    - G (Box 32:, Folder 21)
    - Genetics Department - Arthur Chovnick (Box 32:, Folder 22)
    - Gill, Joseph N. (Trustee) (Box 32:, Folder 23)
    - Gleason, John (Box 32:, Folder 24)
    - Governor of Connecticut - John N. Dempsey (Box 32:, Folder 25)
    - Gr (Box 32:, Folder 26)
    - Health services - Dr. LeRoy, director (Box 32:, Folder 27)
    - Hewitt, H. H. - Dean of Pharmacy (Box 32:, Folder 28)
    - Hillside dormitories (Box 32:, Folder 29)
    - Holt, Guy B. (Trustee) (Box 32:, Folder 30)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. - Dean of Law (Box 32:, Folder 31)
    - I (Box 32:, Folder 32)
    - Inaugurations (Box 32:, Folder 33)
    - Institute of Cellular Biology (Box 32:, Folder 34)
    - Institute - Counseling and guidance training - E. A. Wicas (Box 32:, Folder 35)
    - Institute - food science and nutrition (Box 32:, Folder 36)
    - Institute of Gerontology - Don P. Kent, 1961-1962 (Box 32:, Folder 37)
    - Institute of Labor Management (Box 32:, Folder 38)
    - Institute of Marine Research - John S. Rankin (Box 32:, Folder 39)
    - Institute of Public Service (Box 32:, Folder 40)
    - Institute for Teachers of Science (Box 32:, Folder 41)
    - J (Box 32:, Folder 42)
    - Joint Projects office (Box 32:, Folder 43)
    - Jorgensen, A. N. (Box 32:, Folder 44)
    - K (Box 32:, Folder 45)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 32:, Folder 46)
    - L (Box 32:, Folder 47)
    - Land Grant College Association (Box 32:, Folder 48)
    - Legislature, Federal (Box 32:, Folder 49)
    - Legislature, State (Box 32:, Folder 50)
    - Liaison Committee - Bd. Of Trustees and State Dept. of Education (Box 32:, Folder 51)
    - Library - James E. Skipper (Box 32:, Folder 52)
    - Lo (Box 32:, Folder 53)
    - M (Box 32:, Folder 54)
    - May, Elizabeth E. - Dean, School of Home Economics (Box 32:, Folder 55)
    - McMahon, Brien - Lecture Series (Box 32:, Folder 56)
    - Military ball (Box 32:, Folder 57)
    - Military day (Box 32:, Folder 58)
    - Military department (Box 32:, Folder 59)
    - Mo (Box 32:, Folder 60)
    - N (Box 32:, Folder 61)
    - N. A. B. - National Association of Broadcasters (Box 32:, Folder 62)
    - National Association of State Universities (Box 32:, Folder 63)
    - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 32:, Folder 64)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 32:, Folder 65)
    - Nelson, Donald E. (Box 32:, Folder 66)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 32:, Folder 67)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (Box 32:, Folder 68)
    - New England Land Grant Colleges and State Universities (Box 32:, Folder 69)
    - Norris, Robert - Dean, Continuing Education Services (Box 32:, Folder 70)
    - Northby, Arwood - Dean of Students (Box 32:, Folder 71)
    - Nuclear center (Box 32:, Folder 72)
    - O (Box 32:, Folder 73)
    - P (Box 32:, Folder 74)
    - Peterson, M. Elizabeth (Trustee) (Box 32:, Folder 75)
    - Powers, John E. - Director of Placement (Box 32:, Folder 76)
    - Public Works Department (Box 32:, Folder 77)
    - Q (Box 33:, Folder 1)
    - R (Box 33:, Folder 2)
    - Real estate, 1961-1962 (Box 33:, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations (Box 33:, Folder 4)
    - Religious education (Box 33:, Folder 5)
    - Research foundation (Box 33:, Folder 6)
    - Research grants (Box 33:, Folder 7)
    - Ro (Box 33:, Folder 8)
    - Ryan, J. Ray (Trustee) (Box 33:, Folder 9)
    - S (Box 33:, Folder 10)
    - Sanders, William J. (Trustee) (Box 33:, Folder 11)
    - Sch (Box 33:, Folder 12)
    - Schneller, Richard F. (Trustee) (Box 33:, Folder 13)
    - Scholarships and gifts (Box 33:, Folder 14)
    - Science talent (Box 33:, Folder 15)
    - Selective Services (Box 33:, Folder 16)
    - Sistare, William - Mgr., University auditorium (Box 33:, Folder 17)
    - Sm (Box 33:, Folder 18)
    - South dormitory (Box 33:, Folder 19)
    - Speaking engagements - regrets (Box 33:, Folder 20)
    - St (Box 33:, Folder 21)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 33:, Folder 22)
    - State Building Commission (Box 33:, Folder 23)
    - State Highway Department (Box 33:, Folder 24)
    - State Personnel Department (Box 33:, Folder 25)
    - State Police Department (Box 33:, Folder 26)
    - Student administration group (Box 33:, Folder 27)
    - Student Senate (Box 33:, Folder 28)
    - Student Union Board and Building (Box 33:, Folder 29)
    - Summer theatre (Box 33:, Folder 30)
    - T (Box 33:, Folder 31)
    - Tickets (Box 33:, Folder 32)
    - To (Box 33:, Folder 33)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 33:, Folder 34)
    - Travel (Box 33:, Folder 35)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. - School of Social Work (Box 33:, Folder 36)
    - U (Box 33:, Folder 37)
    - U.S.D.A. (Box 33:, Folder 38)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 34:, Folder 1)
    - University band (Box 34:, Folder 2)
    - University scholars (Box 34:, Folder 3)
    - University secondary school (Box 34:, Folder 4)
    - University Senate (Box 34:, Folder 5)
    - V (Box 34:, Folder 6)
    - Vo - Ag Center (Box 34:, Folder 7)
    - Von der Mehden, J. Louis Rehearsal and Recital Hall, 1961-1962 (Box 34:, Folder 8)
    - W (Box 34:, Folder 9)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 34:, Folder 10)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 34:, Folder 11)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 34:, Folder 12)
    - Wh (Box 34:, Folder 13)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. - Dean, Graduate School (Box 34:, Folder 14)
    - W.H.U.S. (Box 34:, Folder 15)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. - Dean, School of Nursing (Box 34:, Folder 16)
    - X - Y (Box 34:, Folder 17)
    - Young, W. B. Dean, School of Agriculture (Box 34:, Folder 18)
- Series II: Subject Files, 1935-1962
  - Free Speech Issue
    - Telegram (Box 35:, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 35:, Folder 2)
    - McCracken, 1935 April - July (Box 35:, Folder 3-4)
    - Wilbur Cross, 1935 April - May (Box 35:, Folder 5)
    - Arthur Greene, Board of Trustees, 1935 April - June (Box 35:, Folder 6)
    - Albert N. Jorgensen, 1935 March - September (Box 35:, Folder 7)
    - Other persons, 1935 March - September (Box 35:, Folder 8)
    - Petitions from colleges (Box 35:, Folder 9-10)
    - From letters of protest (Box 35:, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda, statements (Box 35:, Folder 12)
    - Publications (Box 35:, Folder 13)
  - Regulations & Policies
    - Academic freedom, academic tenure and Retirement, 1946 (Box 35:, Folder 14)
    - Accreditation (Box 35:, Folder 15)
    - Administrative council, agendas and Presentations (Box 35:, Folder 16)
    - Appointment policy, filling of vacancies and new positions, 1952 (Box 35:, Folder 17)
    - Athletic Policy, 1950 (Box 35:, Folder 18)
    - Auditorium building, Regulations Governing use (Box 35:, Folder 19)
    - Board of Trustees, length of service, Powers and duties (Box 35:, Folder 20)
    - Bond issue schedules, self-liquidating bonds (Box 35:, Folder 21)
    - Building lots, Ledgebrook and North Eagleville, 1949 (Box 35:, Folder 22)
    - Bus Policy, 1953 (Box 35:, Folder 23)
    - Busses, 1961-1962 (Box 35:, Folder 24)
    - Certificates, policy regarding awarding, 1953 September 28 (Box 35:, Folder 25)
    - Changing of classes, consolidation of schedules, 1947 (Box 35:, Folder 26)
    - Commissioner of Education, state department of education (Box 35:, Folder 27)